bestpricedfurniture.com 2012-10-11

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

BestPricedFurniture.com, Inc. ("BestPricedFurniture.com") has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate its strong commitment to the privacy of our visitors and customers. This privacy policy explains how Best Priced Furniture.com collects, uses, shares and protects information obtained from www.bestpricedfurniture.com.

Best Priced Furniture.com has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program only covers information that is collected through the Web site, www.bestpricedfurniture.com. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at privacy@bestpricedfurniture.com If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

**Collection and Use of Information**

BestPricedFurniture.com may collect and store personally identifiable information such as name, email, address, phone and credit card information about persons who visit this site in order for us to process your order. BestPricedFurniture.com may also collect and store aggregate or anonymous information about the user contact with and use of the site. We may use the information to contact you about our products and services or those of our clients from time to time. To opt out of receiving these communications, you can use the unsubscribe link in the email or you can contact us using the information provided in "Contacting the Web Site".We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties or mass marketers. For example, we will not sell another company your name or email address. Unless you consent to the disclosure of your personally identifiable information, only we and our affiliates, our technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality, or provide associated services have access to this information, and we require them to agree that they are covered by this policy. Please note that we do reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information to our successors in business and purchasers of site assets.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as email communications, payment processing and live chat. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

We may also disclose your personal information: 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 
  * if BestPricedFurniture.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, 
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

**Tracking Technologies**

_Cookies_

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We may send your Web browser a "cookie", a small data file that's stored in your hard drive, to help us provide you with customized services. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer. 

_Third Party Cookies_

The use of cookies by third parties is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

_Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_

Our third party advertising partner employs] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 

**Social Media (Features) and Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**Public Forums**

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@bestpricedfurniture.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update or delete inaccuracies by making changes on your Login page or by emailing our us at privacy@bestpricedfurniture.com or by contacting us by the information below.

Our Web site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from BestPricedFurniture.com at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This Web site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database in or order to discontinue future communications or to no longer receive our service.

  1. You can an send email to privacy@bestpricedfurniture.com 
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address: BestPricedFurniture.com   
23505 Crenshaw Blvd. Suite 169   
Torrance, CA 90505-5225 USA 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 310-320-1400

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at the above contact information. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Children's Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of the young (i.e. individuals under the age of 13) is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know who are under 13, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under 13. If a child has provided us with personal information, we ask that a parent or guardian of the child contact us, if they would like the information submitted by a child deleted from our database. We will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Anti-Spam Policy**

BestPricedFurniture.com practices permission-based email marketing. BestPricedFurniture.com does not send unsolicited email or associate with companies who do so.

**Client Databases**

BestPricedFurniture.com stores database lists from our customers. These lists contain email addresses and other demographic information. A customer list is never shared with any other companies, and is regarded as a confidential asset of BestPricedFurniture.com. Confidentiality of the customer is the top priority. We do not sell or rent out the mailing lists of our customers without their consent.

**Links**

The BestPricedFurniture.com website contains links to other sites. BestPricedFurniture.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We recommend users read the privacy policies of each website. 

**Security**

BestPricedFurniture.com has taken all the necessary procedures to ensure a safe visit to our site.

Bestpricedfurniture.com has installed a VeriSign Server ID, which provides our site with complete security and helps make BestPricedFurniture.com a trustworthy Internet experience for our customers. BestPricedFurniture.com uses VeriSign's Payflow Pro to for the secure acceptance and processing of on-line payments. Payflow Pro creates a dedicated SSL TCP/IP level communication thread for each transaction between the client and the server, resulting in outstanding security.

BestPricedFurniture.com has installed industry-standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology to ensure that your information is encrypted. We do not further access any credit card information you provide. Your credit card information will not be shared with any company outside of BestPricedFurniture.com and will only be used for the sole purpose of processing your order. Your personal information is important to us, and we, do not sell, share, or otherwise disclose any personal information gathered from our customers for commercial purposes.

Access to computer data and files at BestPricedFurniture.com are secured by password-protected services. Our network is protected by a firewall designed to protect unauthorized access.

**Privacy Precautionary Warning**

Please note that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit via our online services.

Please note that we reserve the right to access and/or disclose the user information discussed herein (including personal information) as required by courts and/or administrative agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of law or our Site Terms of Use or policies.

**Consent**

By using our Site, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your personal and non-personal information as described in this policy. You further authorize the export of personal information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy when you provide such information to us.

**Notice**

BestPricedFurniture.com reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

**Governing Laws**

BestPricedFurniture.com has its headquarters in Torrance, California. This site as well as these rules are subject to the laws of the State of California and the USA, regardless of the location of the user, and any claims of any kind related thereto must be filed in the courts located in City of Torrance and State of California.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Best Priced Furniture.com, Inc.  
2401 W. 208th Street Suite 9  
Torrance, CA 90501-7259  
or  
privacy@bestpricedfurniture.com
